Madam, how are you?
You have the spirit of suicide.
Yes.
You want to commit suicide.
Yes, sir.
You have depression - serious depression
Yes, serious depression.
Three times you attempted to commit suicide.
Yes, Man of God.
Your family serves gods.
Yes.
Strong gods. They serve gods.
Yes, Man of God.
Why do you want to commit suicide?
Because I was depressed and encountered a lot of difficulties in my life
and I just felt that there are times I cannot cope.
I feel that many people are against me and I don't know them at all.
But I really feel that they are against me, and I also don't know why.
Come on.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
I command every spirit and I command them out in the name of Jesus -
the spirit of suicide and depression caused by generational curses.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
She is free.
Thank You, Jesus!
TESTIMONY TIME
My name is Evelyn and I come from Malaysia.
Last week, the man of God prophesied to me that I had the spirit of committing suicide,
serious depression and that my family serves gods.
They are taoists. They worship three idols at my house and they are conventional Chinese gods.
The name of the god is ... and another one is ancestral spirit.
Another one is the god of lands.
I was brought up worshipping these gods from when I was very young.
I would burn incense and offer it to these gods.
I would offer a sacrifice like roasted chicken, vegetables and also fruits to the idols.
Exactly as Prophet T.B. Joshua said that there were some gods that our sister's family worshipped
She's explaining that right from a young age, she was brought up worshiping three different gods
and making sacrifices to them. Now tell us - as you were growing up,
how did this begin to affect your life negatively?
I have been suffering from depression for many years.
I have always been wanting to commit suicide.
There is one time that I almost wanted to go and jump off from a ten to twenty storey building in Singapore.
There are many times that I tried to kill myself with a knive and get hit by a car.
What was it that was pushing you to attempt suicide?
I kept on hearing voices that I'm a useless person.
I might just as well die. That there was no hope and nothing inside of me.
I did not possess anything. I had no career and no marriage. I should just go and die.
So you would hear these voices talking to you, pushing you into attempting suicide.
You said that you've attempted suicide on many occasions.
Yes, on many occasions.
Whenever I was at home or at work, the thoughts would just come that I should commit suicide.
You mentioned depression as well.
How did that depression - apart from pushing you to attempt suicide - affect you
in your relationships and work? How did that depression really affect?
It lead to failure in my career.
Many times I had to resign from my work.
I also did not have a good relationship with other people.
So the depression really made me to face a lot of difficulties in my life.
But thank God that I was delivered and I'm delivered.
Hallelujah! Now before talking about your deliverance, we want to find out -
how did you come to find out about The SCOAN and Prophet T.B. Joshua?
You said you came all the way from Malaysia, Asia, to be here.
How did you initially discover this ministry?
When I was a buddhist 14 years ago, at the age of 16,
I had a friend who is a Christian.
She gave me a CD of this ministry, of Prophet T.B. Joshua performing miracles.
God is performing miracles through the man of God.
There are many healings and miracles that I witnessed with my own eyes through the CD.
At that time I did not commit myself to Christ.
I just wondered, "Wow, such miracles!
There is really a God in this world!" But I was a Buddhist at that time.
After I witnessed these miracles, I started to believe that there is a God in this world
and I asked my Christian friends to take me to church.
Eventually, I became a Christian after witnessing the works of the man of God.
14 years ago, someone gave you a CD which contained clips from this ministry, The SCOAN.
Yes.
Wow! So we can just imagine what our sister is saying -
right there in Malaysia, she actually saw the video clips of this ministry 14 years ago.
At that time, she had another faith; she was not a Christian.
But the miracles she saw actually convinced her that Jesus Christ was alive
and that led her to the point of becoming a Christian later on.
So tell us - how did you now come to be here today?
I've been trying to come here for many times but I was always facing difficulties,
like "Oh, never mind! You don't need to come!"
"You don't have the money to book the flight ticket' or "Never mind, you just sit at home
and you can watch the screen". But at one point in time before I came, I had a dream.
I saw the man of God. He prophesied to me, and he delivered me.
So this was my decision to eventually come here.
Wow. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So even before physically coming to The SCOAN, you saw Prophet T.B. Joshua in a dream
and God used him to prophesy and to deliver you.
When you finally came, tell us - what happened to you last week?
When he prophesied and prayed for me, I felt that...
When he touched me, I thought there was lightning and a bolt that struck my head
and then immediately I fell down.
Wow. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So the exact problem you came all the way from Malaysia with, was this spirit of suicide,
this spirit of depression. The man of God walked up to you and gave you that exact prophecy -
exactly as you'd seen happen in your dream, even before coming here.
Yes.
And then he prayed for you. Now ever since the prayer you received, just tell us what has happened to your life.
Ever since last week that the man of God prophesied to me, I have no thoughts of committing suicide at all.
Even when I feel bad at times, I no longer have thoughts of committing suicide at all.
Thank God.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Apart from suicidal thoughts that have gone, how have you been relating with others?
You said before that you were always depressed but since that deliverance last week,
how has your life been?
I've become happier, and I do not hold grudges towards other people.
Thank You, Jesus Christ. This is the evidence of the deliverance that our sister received last week.
We can see on the screen how she received that word of prophecy -
the exact problem she came here all the way from Malaysia with.
We give glory to God that she's here as a living testimony today
because this issue of committing suicide and depression is a problem that so many people,
especially young people all over the world, are suffering from.
Our sister had that problem before. She said that she had attempted suicide so many times,
to the point of even trying to jump off a 20-storey building but today she is delivered.
We want to ask you sister: What is your advice to people out there who also have that same problem?
They're depressed. They're feeling of committing suicide, attempting suicide.
What do you want to advise them based on your own deliverance?
Depression comes from holding a grudge towards others.
So my advice is: Do not hold a grudge towards your neighbours or your enemies.
Love your neighbours and your enemies and pray for them.
Then you won't be committing suicide, you won't have the thoughts of committing suicide anymore.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Sister, you said before that you were hearing a voice that was speaking to you,
always pushing you to attempt suicide, to kill yourself, to end it all.
Just describe - since your deliverance last week,
what are the changes you've experienced in your mind, in your heart now concerning that voice?
I don't hear any voice that asks me to commit suicide anymore.
Instead I hear voices of encouraging me in prayer and in loving others.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
This is the evidence of our sister's deliverance that spirits that were pushing her to commit suicide,
that had entered her right from a young age as a result of the gods that her family worshipped
left her after the deliverance and today, we thank God that she's free
and no longer has any thoughts of committing suicide.
One more time, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So right now sister, what is your advice to our viewers all over the world?
My advice is: Get used to challenges.
God has not promised that we as Christians will not encounter challenges
but the way that we handle the challenges will determine our future.
Love your neighbours and love your enemies as yourself,
and there will always be hope in you in Christ Jesus.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!